{
    "subject": "resource/Frank_Archibald_MacDougall",
    "predicate": "ontology/birthPlace",
    "object": "resource/Canada",
    "human_readable": "Frank Archibald MacDougall was born in Canada.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9869847297668457,
            "question": "Is Canada the place of birth for Frank Archibald MacDougall?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.967212975025177,
            "question": "Is Frank Archibald MacDougall Canadian?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9411994814872742,
            "question": "Where was Frank Archibald MacDougall born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.92522794008255,
            "question": "Did Frank Archibald MacDougall spend his childhood in Canada?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7966236472129822,
            "question": "Can you tell me about Frank Archibald MacDougall's birthplace?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7703917026519775,
            "question": "Where did Frank Archibald MacDougall originate from?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.752648651599884,
            "question": "What nationality is Frank Archibald MacDougall?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7059129476547241,
            "question": "What country is Frank Archibald MacDougall from?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5941344499588013,
            "question": "What are some facts about Frank Archibald MacDougall?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4983213543891907,
            "question": "What is known about Frank Archibald MacDougall's early life?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Frank Archibald MacDougall was born in Canada.",
            "html": "dbpedia_7080_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are some facts about Frank Archibald MacDougall?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7080_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What country is Frank Archibald MacDougall from?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7080_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What nationality is Frank Archibald MacDougall?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7080_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7080_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7080_17.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7080_24.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7080_26.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7080_27.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7080_30.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7080_35.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7080_39.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7080_47.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7080_6.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n``` \n\n\nThe provided text states Frank Archibald MacDougall was born on June 16, 1896. It also mentions he was a Canadian pioneering forest ranger in Ontario, Canada.  However, it does not explicitly state where he was *born*. \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Based on the provided context information, I can evaluate the query \"Frank Archibald MacDougall was born in Canada.\"\n\nHere is my response:\n\n`{'output': 'yes'}`\n\nExplanation:\nThe first document mentions that Frank Archibald MacDougall (16 June 1896 \u2013 27 June 1975) was a Canadian pioneering forest ranger. This indicates that he was indeed born in Canada."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information provided in the documents states that Frank Archibald MacDougall was a Canadian pioneering forest ranger and provides his birth date as 16 June 1896, indicating he was born in Canada."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Very Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "gemma2": {
            "reason": "The provided text states Frank Archibald MacDougall was a pioneering forest ranger in Ontario, Canada, and known as the \"flying Superintendent of Algonquin Park\".",
            "category": 2
        }
    }
}